So guys, in today's video I will
tell you how you can buy health insurance from FP, that is,
friends, how can you buy
health insurance for yourself or your family using FP,
so friends,
first of all you have to open your PhonePe application,
after this you have to
scroll down your page here,
friends, here you will
see a tab of insurance here
and friends, here you will see
health insurance on the third number, so
friends, if your
PhonePe health insurance is not shown here, then simply
you have to
tap on view all in the insurance tab, so as soon as
you tap on view all, you have to
come down here and as soon as you
come down here, friends, you will see the
option here of
insure self and family, in
which you will see health insurance here, so
simply friends, you tap on it,
friends, as soon as you tap on it here, guys, a
page like this will
open here, so  Friends, after this
you have to select for whom you
want to buy insurance, that is,
for whom you want to buy health insurance here, so
friends, if
you want to buy health insurance for yourself here, then
you select yourself, that is,
select my self, if you
want to buy health insurance for your
wife here, then
you
select them too, apart from this, if you want to select health insurance
for your entire family here, then
you select them too,
like friends, for example, I will
show you here by buying health insurance only for myself, that is, only for myself, and friends, you can combine the
health insurance for your family or other persons here
in the same step, so
friends, simply you have to
type your age here and after this here  But your
pin code will be of your area,
friends, you simply fill the pin code of your area,
after this you will see the option below here, does
any member have any pre-
registered
disease, if yes then simply you have to tap on yes,
if not then you have to tap on no,
after this friends you have to select view plans
here and guys
follow the same step, if you want to select family or
children or parents, that is, you
want to get their health insurance done here along
with you, then simply friends you have to tap on view plans, so
guys what will happen is that on the phone, the
health insurance plan which will be good for you will be
shown to you here, like friends, you
can see the cover amount here at the top, the
cover amount will be shown here on the
top, after this, the
policy duration will be shown here on the right side, that is,
one year, so guys, if you
want to increase it from one year here, you can increase it here by two years here
According to you friends, you can select the policy here for three years,
so friends,
as you come down here, you get to
see different health
insurance plans here, as you can
see here, it is written Lowest Price
Ever, so you can see it here and
friends, at the same time, by tapping on the more option, you
can check all the details of that particular plan here,
as friends, you can see it here,
apart from this, guys, you will get to
see different plans of health
insurance here and guys, let me tell you
that if you have selected yourself here, then a
different plan for that will be
shown to you and it also depends on your age, so
here on the phone, the
health insurance which will be the best plan for you will be shown to you here,
like friends, for
example, if you want to do
health insurance for your family here, then
you have to tap on edit at the
top, as I have selected
parents here.  But
I have also selected spouse, son, daughter here,
after this, the age of the
elder member of self and spouse will be shown here, that is,
friends, you have to fill their age here, who is the
highest in your family here, that is, if you
select self, my self, spouse, then
whoever is older than you, simply
you have to select him here, then
here you will get to
see the option of add number of children here, like
for example, in friends, I keep 32 here
and you will get to see the option of add number
of children, if there is one child, then you
select one, if there are two, then you
select as per your wish, after that you will get to
see the option of friends here, does any
member have any pre-assisting disease, if yes, then
you have to say yes, if not, then say no,
you have to tap on view plans, so
as soon as you select friends here,
you will get to
see different plans here, like
here  You can see friends and also
here you will get to see the price option in short buy,
here from low to high, that is,
friend, the plans that you will get to see here
and here from lower price to higher
price, you will get to see here and at the same time, you
can change the policy duration here as per your choice, from year to year, three years, like I
showed you three years here, so here you are getting to
see different plans friends,
so whichever plan you like here,
first of all friends, you have to go to
show more here, after that you have to
see those plans carefully here
whether that plan is right for you or not,
you all should read their terms and conditions
and the download policy brochure that you get to see,
you should tap on the download option and
see that policy carefully whether it is
right for you or not, apart from this,
if you need any help
in understanding the policy, then you can also tap on the neat help option
here, like
friends, for example, if you  If you want to
buy any policy
of health insurance from PhonePe here, then you have to
tap on Buy Plan, so friends, as you
will tap on Buy Plan, after this, here
you will get an option of My Self Enter
PAN Number, so friends, if you
select My Self here, then here
friends, you have to
fill your PAN card number here,
your phone number, after that
your gender, your date of birth, weight, your
height, feet, you have to fill the height here, after this you have to fill your weight,
after this your spouse, that is,
your wife's name, wife or
husband, whatever it is, you have to fill their name here, their
last name, their date of birth, their
height, weight, then the name of the children,
their last name,
you have to fill all their details here, so
as soon as you fill here, friends,
after that you will have to tap on Continue friends, so
friends, as
soon as you tap on Continue here,
after that friends, you will have to fill the health details here  The
option of which will be seen here on the second
number, friends, what you have to do in it is that
after filling all the details of whatever health condition your family has, you will have to tap on continue here
and as soon as you tap on continue,
you will have to fill in whatever health
insurance amount is there here,
after that your
health insurance will start here,
apart from this guys, let me tell you
that the procedure of all the health insurances here is a
little
different here, so if you have any
doubt or question here, then you can check it thoroughly
with the PhonePe team or whatever health insurance you buy by tapping on the Neat Help option,
after that you can buy it if you want, so
friends, you can
easily buy PhonePe health insurance by using all these steps, if you have
any question or doubt regarding this,
then please ask me in the comments.